ACTWU Motion Picture Films 5619 F
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 11th Biennial Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America Convention, 1936 -- Cleveland Convetion (Box 35)
  [1a,b,d] - 1936; 16 mm; good, all 4 reels; Black and White; On Reel; Positive; English; 1936 ACWA Convention in Cleveland, OH; Parade; speech; Sidney Hillman; Joseph Scholssberg; Franklin Roosevelt; Canada. This film is a compilation of silent footage from the 1936 convention. The film uses subtitles provided between frames Film 1A: This is the opening of the convention. The films shows delegates on the train arriving in Cleveland and a parade welcoming the members to the convention. The opening session is seen and presided over by General President Sidney Hillman. Hillman introduces General Secretary-Treasurer Joseph Schlossberg. Film 1B: It shows various key union speakers telling their stories and extending their praises to the members of the ACWA including Franklin Roosevelt. The film also shows members voting on various resolutions that were brought up during the convention. Film 1C: This reel begins with the ACWA's Canadian Delegation and their involvement in the convention, also the CIO Chairman speaks and thanks the ACWA for their help in a recent strike. Speakers here discuss the need for new legislation to be passed and a push for union political action. Film 1D: This reel is comprised of the different union committees giving their reports on the status of the union and the goals for that year. The film also covers the Grand Ball which is held before the last day of the convention. The final session includes President Hillman and Vice President Schlossberg being reelected to their positions as well as selecting Atlantic City as the site for their next convention. The film ends with the words: "Glory, Glory, Amalgamated". 1936 ACWA Convention, safety film, subtitles between frames, Films # 1A, (11 min. long. ) 1B (2 copies) (12 min. long. ), 1C (10 min. long) and 1D (11 min. long), Box 4 Union Label Out-takes 1950; 16 mm; good; Black and White; On Reel; Positive; English; Out-takes, footage of clothing workers This is a series of outs from the film "Union Label". It is a short compilation of cuts showing employees in the clothing industry doing their job tasks. Union Label -Outs, 5 min. long. Footage edited out of the film "Union Label" -- 400 feet of film (x2)
- 1940 Convention (Box 36)
  [16] - inside says TWUA 1938 Picnic -- 110 feet of film
- Hillman - We Mourn Our Loss, 1946 (Box 37)
  [3] - Public Affairs Films Inc. 1946; 16 mm; good; Black and White; On Reel; Positive; English; Death of Sidney Hillman, founder of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, This is a short film documenting the death of Sidney Hillman. It discusses the funeral and mourning ceremonies for this popular labor leader. It also discusses a bit about his life and times. It is a tribute film put out by the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America to their founder and President. We Mourn our Loss, 10 min. long. Safety film -- 300 feet of film
- Outs from Union Label (Box 38)
  [17] -- 150 feet of film
- Last grave at Dimbaza (Box 39)
  [108] - 350 feet of film
- Mother is on Strike (Box 40)
  [19] - 16 mm; good; Black and White; On Reel; Positive; English; ILGWU Strike at Tex-son Clothing Company, San Antonio, Texas; Union Label. This film is a short film by the ILGWU informing viewers about the strike at the Tex-son Company in San Antonio, Texas by ILGWU members. The film talks about why the workers are on strike, the strikebreakers, and urges the audience to buy only clothing with the ILGWU label on it. Mother is on Strike, 5 min. long. Safety film -- 225 feet fof film
- How To Bury the Taft-Hartley Act (Box 41)
  [18] - CIO Dept. of Education and Research; 16 mm; good (both prints); Black and White; On Reel; Positive; English; CIO efforts to repeal Taft-Hartley This film is comprised of a series of still pictures and drawings. It is a film put out by the CIO in an effort to gain support for its campaign to repeal the Taft-Hartley Act. The film urges the audience to vote democratic and write to their representatives to let them know how they feel about Taft-Hartley. It also asks that support be given to the Lesinki Bill, which would reverse Taft-Hartley's negative affects on unions. How To Bury the Taft-Hartley Act, 11 min. long -- 400 feet film
- Laundry center dedication (Box 42)
  [40] - 225 feet of film
- Silver Jubilee Banquet, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1939 (Box 43)
  [22] - January 14, 1939, Netherland Plaza -- 250 feet of film
- Joe Davis - American (Box 44)
  [27] -- 300 feet of film
- Chicago Joint Board, Friday April 29 (Box 45)
  [33] -- 400 feet of film
- ACTWU on Strike in New York City (Box 46)
  [23] - 1976; 16 mm; good; Color; On Reel; Positive; English; Strike, ACTWU, New York, 1976, factory. This film is a series of clips from a strike in New York City in 1976. The film shows the strikers walking the line outside the factory as well as shots from inside the sweatshop, where no work is being done. ACTWU on Strike in New York City, 10 min. long, safety film, Film 23, Box 5 ACWA Chicago Joint Board Office ACWA; 16 mm; good; Black and White; On Reel; Positive; English; ACWA Chicago This film is a silent projection of scenes from inside the office of the ACWA Chicago Joint Board. There are also clips from inside various offices in the building including the Secretary-Treasurer of the Board and other officials. ACWA Chicago Joint Board Office, 10 min. long, safety film -- 325 feet of film
- ACWA Boycott Picket in New York City (Box 47)
  [24] - ACWA 1970's; 16 mm; good; Color; On Reel; Positive; English; ACWA, boycott, Macy's, New York City, Farah, picketing, leafletting. This film is comprised of footage taken at a boycott picket of Farah Clothing Products in front of Macy's New York. The films shows members of the ACWA walking the picket line, holding signs, and leafletting pedestrians. ACWA Boycott Picket in New York City, 12 min. long. Safety film -- 375 feet of film
- Keynee Company Strike (Box 48)
  [13] - 16 mm; good; Black and White; On Reel; Positive; English; Keynee Company strike; Cleveland, Ohio, pickets This is a short silent film that shows the strike at the Keynee Company in Cleveland, OH. Most of the scenes are of strikers walking the line and cheering. No other information is given on the film. Keynee Company Strike, 8 min. film -- 250 feet of film
- Shirtmakers Day (Box 49)
  [15] - 16 mm; good; Black and White; On Reel; Positive; English; Clothing Workers, parade This is a film that shows the events of Shirtmaker's Day including learning sessions, a dinner reception, and a parade to celebrate the event. Shirtmaker's Day, 12 min. long. -- 400 feet of film
- Too dark too fast (Box 50)
  [7] -- 250 feet of film
- It's Been Good to Know You (Box 51)
  [88] - Harold Mayer Production; 16 mm; good (both prints); Color; On Reel; Positive; English; ACWA, Phillips Van-Heusen Boycott; plant closing. This is a short promotional film put out by the ACWA to encourage consumers to boycott the Phillips Van-Heusen Clothing Company. The company closed numerous plants in Pennsylvania, Alabama, and Arkansas, before moving the operations to Asia. The motivation behind these closings is assumed to be labor costs associated with both union and non-union workforces in the United States. The film urges consumers not to purchase the products made by Phillips Van-Heusen. It's Been Good to Know You, 13 min. long, safety film -- 350 feet of film
- You next President [Jimmy Carter], 1976 (Box 52)
  moved to 5619F from 5619 AV box 6 -- 500 feet of film
- Contract Contract, 1975 (Box 53)
  [87] - TWUA 1975, revised 1987; 16 mm; very poor, sprocket holes are damaged or missing early in the film; Black and White; On Reel; Positive; English; Contracts, Oneita Knitting Mill, strikes, Textile Workers *film is damaged and not viewable; summary taken from "Films and Video Tapes for Labor" Film Division, AFL-CIO Department of Education, Revised March 1987.* Bayard Rustin narrates this story of the long struggle of Oneita Knitting Mill workers who fought for a contract 14 months after they won a representation election at the South Carolina textile plant. Workers tell what the union means to them in terms of human dignity, job security, wages and fringe benefits and what they learned when black and white workers joined together to fight for a union. Contract, Contract; film is damaged and in poor condition, sprocket holes are missing, film does not project properly -- 1000 feet of film
- Union local (Box 54)
  [51] -- 1000 feet of film
- Valley of the Tennessee (Box 55)
  [54] -- 1200 feet of film
- Unlabelled (Box 56)
  450 feet of film
- People of the Cumberland (Box 57)
  [42] -- 850 feet of film
- The Dream - Pt. 1 and 2 (Box 58)
  [106] -- 1100 feet of film on 2 reels
- Testimony, Justice Vs. J.P. Stevens (Box 59)
  F13 - moved from 5619 AV, box 7 -- approx. 1200 feet of film
- MacNeil/Lehrer Report J.P. Stevens [broken] (Box 60)
  F11 - moved from 5619 AV, box 7 -- 1000 feet of film
- MacNeil/Lehrer Report J.P. Stevens (Box 61)
  F61 - moved from 5619 AV, box 7 -- 1000 feet of film
- Convention "B" (Box 62)
  moved from 5619 AV, box 25 -- 900 feet of film
- Textile workers panel discussion (Box 63)
  [101] - 1955; 16mm; good, both prints; Black and White; On Reel; Positive; English; Panel Discussion, Textile Workers Union of America, New England Textile Mills, negotiations. The film is a panel discussion by various local leaders of the Textile Workers Union of America (TWUA) from the New England Area. They talk about efficiency and the high profits of New England textile mills and their ability to provide a decent living wage to workers. The panel is upset over negotiations at one of the mills where the employer is offering virtually nothing and the employees plan to strike. Textile Workers Panel Discussion, 16 min. long -- 600 feet of film
- ACWA - 1954 Convention (Box 64)
  700 feet of film
- The Case of Barbara Parsons (Box 65)
  [91] - Pt. 1 of 2 - Morton Parker Arthur Mokier Productions; 16 mm; good; Color; On Reel; Positive; English; Grievance procedure, seniority rights and promotions, arbitration, IUE. This film tells the story of Technical Engineer, Michael Blais. Blais was passed over for a promotion he felt he should have received. Blais has performed well on the job for 19 years while an employee who has only been there 2 months was promoted (Barbara Parsons). Blais, along with his shop steward (IUE), file a grievance and proceed from there. The film follows the course of the grievance through the first 3 steps and then on to arbitration. It shows the different union and management people who handle each step and what role they play. During arbitrations, both Blais and Parsons are called to testify. The arbitrator decides in favor of the union citing that no legitimate reasoning was used when promoting Parsons and not Blais. The Case of Barbara Parsons, 52 min. long. Safety Film -- 1000 feet of film
- AFL-CIO Press Conference, G. Washington Lodge, 1972 (Box 66)
  F3- moved from 5619 AV, box 5 -- 125 feet of film
- Farah boycotts in front of Macy's (Box 67)
  [24] - moved from 5619 AV, box 5 -- 175 feet of film
- Dean Martin Show (Box 68)
  F5 - moved from 5619 AV, box 6 -- 150 feet of film
- Amalgamated protest, 1974 (Box 69)
  F7 - moved from 5619 AV, box 6 -- 400 feet of film
- ACWA - Cultural Conference - Rochester (Box 70)
  moved from 5619 AV, box 6 -- 300 feet of film
- J.P. Stevens, 60 Minutes (Box 71)
  F1 - moved from 5619 AV, box 4 -- approx. 125 feet of film - on a core
- Import demons (Box 72)
  F2 - moved from 5619 AV, box 5 -- 200 feet of film
- Kamber American Shipyard (Box 73)
  F4 - moved from 5619 AV, box 6 -- 350 feet of film
- Gateway to the West; Downtown SF panoramas (Box 74)
  F8 - moved from 5619 AV, box 6 -- 350 feet of film
- Untitled (Box 75)
  F9 - moved from 5619 AV, box 6 -- 300 feet of film
- Americans at work: Utility Workers (Box 76)
  F10 - moved from 5619 AV, box 6 -- 550 feet of film
- Water Spout (Box 77)
  F6 - moved from 5619 AV, box 6 -- 125 feet of film
- Fight for my union (Box 78)
  moved from 5619 AV, box 6 -- 574 feet of film
- The Dreams Continues (Box 79)
  F14 - moved from 5619 AV, box 10 -- 1000 feet of film
- Farah vs. The People (Box 80)
- The Dream Continues - ACTWU (Box 81)
  [95] - Release Print -- 1000 feet of film - 2 reels
- Various S/T OUTS -- ACTWU - 06708 - The Dream; Hands, lay version; Tillet; Opening Music, ACTWU; UN Mod; blank // ACTWU - 06708 (Box 82)
  9 reels - removed from box 18 during reorganization of this collection --- 1300 feet of film (collectively) on cores
- Millwork, Weaving Spools, Cleaning Cotton Cutting (reel #1); Sewing (#2); Copy Machine Maintenance (#3); Shoe Making Assembly Line (#4); Banks, Airlines (Eastern) - Picketing, 1985 (Box 83)
  (text continued from title) - Press Conference #5; Rally for Justice (ACTWU) (#6) // ACTWU - 06708 - Trims -- June 1985 -- 6 Reels -- removed from box 18 during reorganization of this collection -- 1360 feet of film (collectively)
- Asner Narration - OUTS; Asner #1; Asner Narration OUTS #2 //ACTWU -- Archival: TWUA; Women at War // ACTWU -- 06708 (Box 84)
  3 reels -- removed from box 18 during reorganization of this collection -- 1180 feet of film (collectively)
- TWA (reel #90); WW II Film Bulletin, Women at War (reel #95); Marshall Field (roll #3) (Box 85)
  4 reels -- removed from box 14 during reorganization of this collection -- 1625 feet of film (collectively) on cores -- one reel is unlabeled
- Dialog OUTS - New Actress, Retirees changed, Last Dialog, Old Retirees, FDR (more unlabeled) // ACTWU - 06708 (Box 86)
  10 reels -- removed from box 13 during reorganization of this collection -- 705 feet of film (collectively) on cores
- ACTWU "Dream" - J.P. Stevens (Box 87)
  Col. Pos. Print - I/W & W/P -- 4 reels -- removed from box 14 during reorganization of this collection -- 1300 feet of film (collectively)
- ACTWU "Dream" - R-57-61 (Box 88)
  5 reels -- removed from box 14 during the reorganization of this collection -- 1910 feet of film (collectively)
- Factory Interiors: Weaving Mills (#1); Small Hand Work, Sewing Machines (#2); Current Membership at Work // TKG: ACTWU - 06708 - Inheritance; ACTWU (Box 89)
  4 reels - - 1315 feet of film, 3 on cores, 1 film strip; removed from box 14 during the reorganization of this collection
- The Dream Continues - 2/6/1986, Narration (roll #2); Garment District (roll #10) // TKG: ACTWU - 06708 - Inheritance; ACTWU: Current - Members Workers (Box 90)
  Removed from box 8 during the reorganization of this collection -- aprox. 600 feet of film on 2 cores
- Flint Why Strike? (#115); 1903 Lower Broadway; NYC Ghetto Fish market; Lynch Story (#112), a wind master // ACTWU - Archival: Can Q R 112, 115-118 (Box 91)
  8 reels -- removed from box 14 during reorganization of this collection -- 975 feet of film on cores -- untitled reels #116, 117, 118
- ACTWU - "Dream" - Orig. -- Steve York (Box 92)
  13 Reels -- approx. 500 feet of film on 3 cores
- Millwork (roll #12)TKG: ACTWU - 06708 - Inheritance (Box 93)
  Removed from box 8 during reorganization of this collection -- approx. 350 feet of film on a core
- Golf, Parades, Building (roll #13) // TKG - ACTWU - 06708 - Inheritance (Box 94)
  1 reel -- Roll #13 - N/A; Golf, Parades, Building -- FF/0000-1190 -- Removed from box 11 during the reorganization of this collection -- 490 feet of film
- 60 Minutes - J.P. Stevens; Dirty WP; OUTS // TKG - ACTWU - 06708 - Inheritance (Box 95)
  Track and Film; 4 reels -- Removed from box 4 during the reorganization of this collection -- 1320 feet of film on cores
- Freedom Haven; News in Brief: Russian aircrafts, Florida: Miss Universe, Sports (Russia); Ghana Revolt (reel #1) - Pres. Johnson giving Goldstar Picketing against Castro (reel #2) // TKG: ACTWU - 06708 - Inheritance (Box 96)
  N/A - Rolls #1 and #2 -- approx. 550 feet of film
- ACTWU: Current Membership Working (Box 97)
  Rolls #5 and #6 -- MOS/Color --- 650 feet of film
- ACTWU: Current Members at Work (Box 98)
  MOS/Color/NP #13 -- 650 feet of film
- 1936 Cleveland Convention (Box 99)
  Reel #1 -- 400 feet of film
- ACTWU -- L. Grey (Box 100)
  "Not Used", Archival -- removed from 5619 F, box 18 -- approx. 600 feet of film
- ACTWU - 06708 -- Union at Work (Box 101)
  Reel 9 -- approx. 825 feet of film on a core
- ACTWU -- Current Membership at Work (Box 102)
  Rolls #13 and #14 -- MOS; Color -- moved from 5619 F, box 5 -- approx. 550 feet of film on a core
- Filmographs (Box 103)
  Reel 5 -- moved from 5619 F, box 16 -- approx. 300 feet of film on a core
- Demonstrations (1B); Street Scenes, ACTWU (1C); FDR/NRA (1D); Yamashita, Truman, Elenor Roosevelt (1E); Misc./ACTWU Crawl (1F) -- ACTWU (Box 104)
  moved from 5619 F, box 16 -- box 1 - approx. 750 feet of film on 5 cores
- Finley Outs- ACTWU (Box 105)
  W/P; Color; Reel 3; moved from 5619 F, box 18 -- approx. 375 feet of film on 4 cores
- ACTWU - A, B: O.C.N.; Solidarity Day (Box 106)
  B S/+; Reel 10; moved from 5619 F, box 16 -- 650 feet of film
- The Good Life: High Tech (Box 107)
  [2 of 2] --Roll 1 and 3; Reel 16; W/P; Color; moved from 5619 F, box 16 -- aprox. 500 feet of film on a core
- Inheritance (Box 108)
  Original film - Reel #2, Roll #1; W/P; Track; moved from 5619 F, box 11 -- approx. 400 feet of film on a core -- TKG: ACTWU - 06708-
- The Dream (3/14/1986) (Box 109)
  Finn/Mix; 16 Mag Safety Reel -- 1000 feet of film
- Berkshire Strike (roll 'C'); Strikes Demo (roll 'D') -- 1979 (Box 110)
  Roll C-HH/0005-0984; Berkshire Strike // Roll D-AB/00074166; Strikes Demo, 1979 -- moved from 5619 F, box 16 -- approx. 490 feet of film on a core -- TKG: ACTWU -06708 - Demonstration
- America Goes Back to Peace (Box 111)
  Roll 7A; Roll 7 is on Roll 9; Roll 8 and 10; GJ/0369-0818 - L. Grey's original; B/W -- 575 feet of film
- Women- WWI - roll 11; WPA, NRA Strikes - roll 12 (Box 112)
  moved from 5619 F, box 13 -- approx. 275 feet of film on a core
- Trims - [5 film strips] // TKG: ACTWU - 06708 - Inheritance (Box 113)
  Reel #2 -- MOX; Color; W/P -- approx. 1200 feet of film on cores
- ACTWU: Current membership at work (Box 114)
  Roll 16 - Cutting, Stitching, Millwork -- TKG: ACTWU-06708 - Inheritance -- MOS; Color; W/P -- 225 feet of film
- ACTWU - "DREAM" -- 2/4/1985 (Box 115)
  R-1A; 1B; 2A; 2B -- approx. 450 feet of film on a core
- ACTWU - "DREAM" (Box 116)
  R-3A -- moved from 5619 F, Box 14 -- approx. 450 feet of film on a core
- ACTWU -- "Dream"-R (Box 117)
  #71 -- moved from 5619 F, box 14 -- 800 feet of film
- ACTWU "DREAM" (Box 118)
  Reel 7; moved from 5619 F, box 14 -- approx. 350 feet of film on a core
- The Dream (Box 119)
  approx. 650 feet of film on 3 cores
- Trims - '85, June -- ACTWU - 06708 (Box 120)
  Reel 8 --Sewing, Cutting, Pressing, Dyeing, Millwork, Pres. Nixon, Shoe making, Fireworks, ACTWU Logo, Close-Ups -- moved from 5619 F, box 18 -- approx. 650 feet of film on a core
- Auto Assembly Immigrants, T. Edison (Box 121)
  ACTWU -- B/W -- Reel 4 -- approx. 275 feet of film
- ACTWU - "Civil War and Revolution War" (Box 122)
  Cut W/P+; (2/28/1985); moved from 5619 F, box 16 -- 650 feet of film
- Various S/T Outs -- ACTWU - 06708 - [3 cores unlabeled] (Box 123)
  moved from 5619 F, box 18 -- 450 feet of film
- ACTWU: Senior Citizens, Members at work (Box 124)
  Rolls 17 and 18 -- TKG: ACTWU-06708--Inheritance -- MOS; Color; W/P -- #18-Shoes, Sewing Shoes -- moved from 5619 F, box 11 -- 400 feet of film
- Historical - U.S. International New, Fashion on Holliday in Hollywood // TKG: ACTWU 06708 - Inheritance (Box 125)
  Roll 5; B/W -- moved from 5619 F, box 11 -- 275 feet of film on a core -- 2 rolls, one is unlabeled, may be roll 6 that is referenced on notes in box with rolls
- Democrats Nominate Kennedy; Africa violence - UN votes to send troops to Congo (Box 126)
  Roll 4; D/N; B/W; N/A -- moved from 5619 F, box 11 -- approx. 210 feel of film on a core
- Asbestos - 80296 -- Dr. Sclikoff (Box 127)
  moved from 5619 F, box 16 -- 2 films one on a core and one film stip -- approx. 875 feet of film
- Tails TKG Asbestos, Sync, Susan Vogt, EPA, Intv. Takes 2-6 (Box 128)
  CR# 101, 102; SR# 101; WP; Track; EE000-0696 -- moved from 5619 F, box 16 -- approx. 625 feet of film on a core
- Kamber -- ACTWU "DREAM" outs (Box 129)
  A and B original cut outs -- 2/28/1986 -- moved from 5619 F, box 15 -- 375 feet of film
- ACTWU: Current Membership Working (Box 130)
  Roll 3 - Ext, NYC -- moved from 5619 F, box 12 -- 400 feet of film
- Textile Mills -- ACTWU: Current Membership Working (Box 131)
  MOS; Color: W/P; Roll #8- -- moved from 5619 F, box 13 -- approx 275 feet of film on a core
- Music Demo // TKG: ACTWU - 06708 - Inheritance (Box 132)
  Music Demo - moved from 5619 F, box 12 -- 650 feet of film on a core
- Market Scene, Street Scenes, 1920; Baseball Voter Lines // TKG: ACTWU - 06708 - Inheritance (Box 133)
  Roll "E" - JJ/0001-0595; Baseball, Voter Lines; B/W; W/P - moved from 5619 F, box 12 -- approx. 750 feet of film on two cores
- Dialog Outs - TKG: ACTWU - 06708 - Inheritance - Roll 1 (Box 134)
  moved from 5619 F, box 12 -- box 1-750 feet of film
- Scenic; Immigrants // TKG: Prod. - 06708 - ACTWU, Inheritance (Box 135)
  B/W; Scenic; Immigrants -- moved from 5619 F, box 12 -- 325 feet of film on two cores
- Charlottsville: Countryside, Colonial Artifacts, Horses, Graveyard, 1700's Documents, Montecello (Jefferson's Home) // TKG: ACTWU - 06708 - Inheritance - Outs (Box 136)
  B/W; W/P -- moved from 5619 F, box 12 -- 800 feet of film on a core
- Southern Milltown / ACTWU -- TKG-06708 - Inheritance (Box 137)
  moved from 5619 F, box 12 -- 190 feet of film on a core
- ACTWU: Inheritance - Roll #2 // TKG: Prod. - 06708 (Box 138)
  W/P; Track; Outs; Original Film -- moved from 5619 F, box 12 -- 1200 feet of film on a core
- ACTWU - Orig.; R146-148 (Box 139)
  Reel 3 -- moved from 5619 F, box 17 -- 300 feet of film
- ACTWU - Fiest (Box 140)
  A/P; W/Mix; moved from 5619 F, box 16 -- approx. 1000 feet of film
- ACTWU -- Kamber Group - 5-18-1984 (Box 141)
  I/N -- Reel 8 -- moved from 5619 F, box 17 -- 875 feet of film on a core
- ACTWU -- "DREAM" (Box 142)
  Reel 2 -- moved from 5619 F, box 15 -- approx. 1000 feet of film on a core
- ACTWU - "DREAMS"; "Wild West Shots" (Box 143)
  Color; Original; moved from 5619 F, box 15 -- 375 feet of film
- ACTWU-- W/P -- "The Dream" (Box 144)
  moved from 5619 F, box 15 -- 1000 feet of film
- Kamber -- ACTWU -- SFX (3-6-1986) (Box 145)
  loose film, no way to measure, in pieces
- National Geo -- Baseball at head // ACTWU - 06708 - l. Grey - Sitdowns from "Babies and Banners" (Box 146)
  Reel 4 -- approx. 400 feet of film on a core
- ACTWU - "DREAM" - Sewing; Housing Ext/Sign CR7, Chicago; ASPLN (Box 147)
  Film, Tracks, CTU, Ftg -- approx. 600 feet of film on 5 cores
- ACTWU: Archival, Parades, Protests, Demos (Box 148)
  approx. 200 feet of film
- ACTWU - WLHFP Animation; F - lint, 7247, Main title; WB + B opticals, Positive; WB + B opticals, color (Box 149)
  WLHFP, Archive -- R-149-156, 158-164; Reel 5; moved from 5619 F, box 17 -- approx. 600 feet of film on 4 cores
- ACTWU - Sewing Assembly; Assembly - Cutting - Sewing (Box 150)
  Roll #15 -- W/P; Color; moved from 5619 F, box 16 --approx. 450 feet of film on a core
- 1941 -- (only information on label) (Box 151)
  moved from 5619 AV, box 6 -- 250 feet of film
- unlabeled (Box 152)
  moved from 5619 AV, box 6 -- 100 feet of film
- Dream - 1st Ang. PRT, PT 2: R#2, FGM (Archives) (Box 153)
- Dream - 1st Ang. PRT, PT 2: R#2, FGM (Archives) (Box 154)
- Poverty in the Valley of Plenty (Box 155)
- 1938 ACWA Convention (Box 156)
  5B -- Reel #2 - no other information available
- 1938 ACWA Convention (Box 157)